TARUNDEEP SINGH WAZIR

Mob.: +91-8899241036 **E-mail:** wazirg10@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVES

I want to work with an organization where I can use my natural skills for the betterment of the organization, which will enhance my knowledge, technical skills, and multitasking ability. And also affect society to make good changes with a positive attitude with the right directions and develops the natural emotions and experience of life.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

Year	University / Boards Exam Passed	Instituti on	Result
2013-20 17	B. Tech in Mechanical	M.M. University Mullana, Ambala,Haryana	PAS S
2012	12th (JK Board)	Saint Joseph Higher SecondarySchool Baramulla	PASS
2010	10th (JK Board)	Saint Joseph Higher SecondarySchool Baramulla.	PASS
2019	MONTREAL CANADA	CEGEP ILES GASPESIA	PASS

INDUSTRIAL EXPOSURE / SUMMER INTERNSHIP

> Completed 6 months Internship with BOSCH.

WORK EXPERIENCE: - (3.5 YEARS)

WORKED AS SALES MANAGER IN UNIVERSAL TECHNO (JAMMU) FROM (14 JULY 2017 to Dec 2019) (14 Nov 2109 -6 NOVEMBER 2021)

WORKING AS SALES EXECUTIVE IN MULTINATIONAL COMPANY "INTEGRATED SERVICESOLUTION GLOBAL FORWARDING (ISSGF)" 15 DEC 2021-PRESENT

AREA OF INTEREST

- > Sales/Marketing
- > Technical
- > Operational
- > Quality Assurance
- > Supply Chain

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- > Secured 5th Position in Fashion Parade in college festival "UNIVERSUMM'16".
- > Represented school in Cricket at the Regional level.
- > Participated in Extempore.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- ➤ Made Gyroscope (Self Balancing of the vehicle on single tire)
- Basic Engine Training
- Fuel Injection System
- Auto Electrical System
- Wheel Balancing System
- ➤ Air Conditioning System
- ➤ ECU Scanner

STRENGTHS

- > A good practical hand.
- Good Communication Skills.
- > Punctuality and Adaptability to any environment and situation.
- > Self-confident.

HOBBIES

- > Playing Cricket and Badminton.
- Listening to music, visiting new places.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Father: Karnail Singh Wazir Date of Birth: 16 May 1994

Languages Known: English, Hindi, Punjabi, Urdu,

French.Country: INDIA

Home Address: Noor Bagh Baramulla Kashmir (J&k)E-mail ID: wazirg10@gmail.com Mobile: 8976715084, 8899241036

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all the information provided by me in this application is correct and factual to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Place: Ludhiana Date: 02-03-2022

(Tarundeep Singh Wazir)